Love to love, love to love
Don't hurt me, don't hurt me
Young money, yeah
Throw dirt on me and grow a wildflower
But it's fuck the world, get a child louder
Yeah, my life a bitch, but you know nothing about her
Been to hell and bang, I can show you vouchers
I'm rolling sweets, I'm smoking sour
Married to the game, but she broke her vows
That's why my bars are full of broken bottles
And my nightstands are full of open bibles
I think about more than I forget
But I don't go around fire expecting not to sweat
And these niggas know I lay them down, make you bed
Bitches try to kick me while I'm down, I break your leg
Money outweighing problems on a triple beam
I'm sticking to the script
You niggas skipping scenes
Uh, be good or be good at it
Fuckin' right, I got my gun, send me card-o-matic
Put the dick in they mouth
So I guess it's fuck what they say
I'm high as a bitch
Up, up and away
Man, I'll come down in a couple of days
Okay, you want me up in a cage
Then I'll come out in beast mode
I got this world stuck in a safe combination
It's the chief code
It's busy motherfucker, blood gang, and I'm in bleed mode
All about my dough, but I don't even check the peephole
So you can keep knockin', but won't knock me down
No love lost, no love found
It's a little too late to say that you're sorry now
You kicked me when I was down, but what you say is
Don't hurt, that's right it don't hurt
I don't need you no more, don't wanna see you
No more, huh, bitch you can't hurt
You show me nothing but hate, you ran me into the ground
But what comes around goes around
And you don't hurt, that's right, you don't hurt
And I don't need you no more, don't wanna see you
Bitch you can't hurt
No love, no love, no love, no love, no love, no love
No love, no love, no love, no love
And I don't need you no more, get em
I'm alive again, more alive than I had been
In my whole entire life I can see these people's ears
Perk up as I begin to spaz with the pen
I'm a little bit sicker than most
Shit's finna get thick again
They say the competition is stiff
But I get a hard dick from this shit
Now stick it in
I ain't never giving in again
Caution to the wind, complete freedom
Look at these rappers, how I treat em
So why the fuck would I join em when I beat em?
They call me a freak cause I like to spit on these pussies for I eat em
Man, get these whack cock suckers off stage
Where the fuck is Kanye when you need em?
Snap the mic from em, bitch
I'ma let you finish in a minute
Yeah, that rap was tight
But I'm fucked with the greatest verse of all time
So you might wanna go back to the lab tonight
And I'm ripple out them rhymes you were gonna spit and start over
Who's scratching right new ones
But I'm afraid that it ain't gonna make no difference
When I rip the stage and tear it in half tonight
It's an adrenaline rush
You feel the bass dunk from the place
All the way to the parking lot, fella
Set fire to the mic and ignite the crowd
You can see the sparks from hot metal
Cold hearted from the day I bogarted the game
My soul started at rock, fella
When I'm not even at my harshest
You can still get roasted, cause marches
Snap mellow till I'm toppling from the top
I'm not gonna stop home
Standing on my monopoly board
That means I'm on top of my game
And it don't stop till my hip don't hop anymore
When you're so good that you can't say it
Cause it ain't even cool for you to sound cocky anymore
People just get sick cause you spit these fools
Can't drool or dribble or drop anymore
And you can never break my stride
You'll never slow the momentum
At any moment I'm bout to blow
You'll never take my pride
I'm killing the flow
Slow venom and the opponent is getting no
Mercy mark my words
Ain't letting up, relentless I smell blood
I don't give a fuck, keep giving them hell
When was you when I found them?
Needed help up, you get no luck
It's a little too late to say that you're sorry now
You kicked me when I was down
But what you say just don't hurt
Yeah, that's right it don't hurt
And I don't need you no more
Don't wanna see you no more
Bitch you get no luck
You show me nothing money
You ran me into the ground
But what comes around, what comes around
And you don't hurt
That's right you don't hurt
And I don't need you no more
Don't wanna see you no more
Bitch you get no luck
No love
And I don't need you no more
Bitch you get no luck
But you need me no true
I'm nothing